Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- A Poetry Newsletter, Albuquerque, New Mexico, #2, December, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Poetry Newsletter, New York City, #2, February, 1965-March, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Poetry Newsletter, New York City, #6, December, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Poetry Newsletter, Scranton, Pennsylvania, #11, undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Poetry Newsletter, Temple University, Philadelphia, #6, May, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Poetry Newsletter, Temple University, Philadelphia, #10, September, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Poetry Newsletter, Temple University, Philadelphia, #12, November, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Poetry Parade, North Hollywood, California, #6, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #2, January, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #3, February, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #4, March, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #5, April, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #6, May, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #7, June, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #34, April, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #35, May, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #40, December, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- The Poetry Project Newsletter, New York City, #41, January, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Poetry Review, University of Tampa, Tampa, Florida, #6, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Poetry Review, University of Tampa, Tampa, Florida, #12, undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Poetry Review, University of Tampa, Tampa, Florida, #14, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Poetry Review, University of Tampa, Tampa, Florida, #15, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Poetry Review, University of Tampa, Tampa, Florida, #16, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Poetry Review, University of Tampa, Tampa, Florida, #17, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Poets at Le Metro, New York City, v. 8, November, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Poets at Le Metro, New York City, v. 18, November, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Poet's Calliope, Tucson, circa 1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #3, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #4, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #5, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #6, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #7, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #8, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #9, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #10, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #11, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #12, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #13, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #14, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #15, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #16, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #17, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #18, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #19, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #20, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #21, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #22, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #23, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #24, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #25, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Poets Gallery, San Francisco, v. 1, #26, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Poets On:, Chaplin, Connecticut, v. 3, #1, Winter (Hurting), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- poets yeggs and thirsties, Boston/Indianapolis, v. 1, #1, Summer, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Pogamoggan, Brooklyn, New York, #1, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Politics & Letters, v. 1, #4, Summer, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #12, undated (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #15, undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #16, undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #17, undated (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #18, undated (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #19, undated (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #20, undated (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #21, undated (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #22, undated (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #24, undated (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Poor Old Tired Horse, Edinburgh, Scotland, #25, undated (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Pot-Hooks & Hangers, New York City, v. 1, #1, Summer, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- The Powys Newsletter, Hamilton, New York, #1, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- The Powys Newsletter, Hamilton, New York, #2, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Presence, Buffalo, New York, #1, Summer, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Presence, Buffalo, New York, #2, Winter, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Presence, Buffalo, New York, #3, Summer, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 54)
- Priapus, Berkhamsted, England, #9, Summer, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Priapus, Berkhamsted, England, #17, Spring, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Priapus, Berkhamsted, England, #18, Summer, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 57)
- Priapus, Berkhamsted, England, #21, Spring, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 58)
- Prickly Pear, Boston, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 59)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #1, August, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 60)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #2, September, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 61)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #3, October, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 62)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #4, November, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 63)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #5, December, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 64)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #6, January, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 65)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #7, February, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 66)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #8, March, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 67)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #9, April, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 68)
- Private Tutor, Nottingham, England, #10, May, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 69)
- The Promethean Lamp, Sacramento, California, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- The Promethean Lamp, Sacramento, California, v. 1, #3, Fall, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Prose, New York City, #1, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Prose, New York City, #2, Spring, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Prose, New York City, #3, Fall, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Prose, New York City, #4, Spring, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Prospect, Cambridge, England, #6, Spring, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Proteus, Alexandria, Virginia, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Pucred, San Francisco, v. 1, #4, April, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Pulse, El Rito, New Mexico, #1, November, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Pulse, El Rito, New Mexico, #2, March, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 1, #1, November, 1966-December, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 2, #11 through v. 4, #18, November, 1966-April, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 4, #20, July, 1970-August, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Punto de Partida, Mexico, v. 4, #22, November, 1970-December, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Pyramid, Belmont, Massachusetts, #1, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Pyramid, Belmont, Massachusetts, #8, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Quark, Iowa City, Iowa, #2, February, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Quark, Reno, Nevada, #1, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Quark, Reno, Nevada, #2, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Quark, Reno, Nevada, #3, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Quarry, Kingston, Canada, v. 15, #3, March, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Quarry, University of California, Santa Cruz, California, #2, Autumn, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Quarterly, Montclair State College, Upper Montclair, New Jersey, v. 40, #4, Winter, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- The Quest, New York City, v. 3, #1, Summer/Fall, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- The Quest, New York City, v. 3, #2, Winter/Spring, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- The Quest, New York City, #3, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- The Question, Albuquerque, New Mexico, v. 1, #1, May, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Quetzal, Water Hole Swamp, North Carolina, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Qui, France, #4, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Quick Anthology, #16, September, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- The Quire, Berkeley, California, v. 2, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 1, #1, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 1, #2, December, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, December, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 4, #2, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 4, #4, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 4, #5, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 4, #6, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 4, #7, undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 4, #8, Spring, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Quixote, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 5, #4, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Quoz?, San Francisco, v. 1, v. 2 (bound together), 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Quoz?, San Francisco, v. 3, #9, March, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Quoz?, San Francisco, #10, Summer, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Quoz?, San Francisco, #11, Autumn, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- R. C. Lion, University of California, Berkeley, California, #2, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- R. C. Lion, University of California, Berkeley, California, #3, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Radical America, Madison, Wisconsin, v. 2, #6, November, 1968-December, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Radical America, Madison, Wisconsin, January, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Radical Theatre Festival, San Francisco State College, San Francisco, September, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Radix, Somerville, Massachusetts, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Radix, Somerville, Massachusetts, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Ragweed Review, Topeka, Kansas, March, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Raices, Mexico, #1, August, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Rainy Day, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, v. 1, #1, April, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Rapport, Buffalo, New York, v. 1, #2-3, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Reach Out, Columbus, Ohio, v. 3, #1 (#10), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- The Rebel, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina, Spring, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- The Record, The Hill School, Pottstown, Pennsylvania, #4, December, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Red Clay Reader, Charlotte, North Carolina, #7, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Red Crow, Gloucester, Massachusetts, #1, Winter, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Red Crow, Gloucester, Massachusetts, #2, Spring, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- The Redneck Review, Houston, Texas, #1, Spring, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- The Reed, San Jose State University, San Jose, California, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Reflections from Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, v. 1, #3, November, 1961-December, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- El Rehilete, Mexico, #19, March, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- El Rehilete, Mexico, #24, August, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- El Rehilete, Mexico, #25, December, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- El Rehilete, Mexico, #26, March, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- El Rehilete, Mexico, #30-31, April, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- El Rehilete, Mexico, #32, July, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Remember Our Fire, San Lorenzo, California, #3, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
- The Remington Review, Elizabeth, New Jersey, #2, October, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Renaissance, East Northport, Long Island, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Renaissance, East Northport, Long Island, v. 1, #3, Spring, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Renaissance, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, January, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Renaissance, San Francisco, v. 1, #3, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Residu, Athens, Greece, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Resistance, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Resurgence, London, England, v. 2, #12 (and New Departures 5), March, 1970-April, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Resusitator, Paulton, England, #5, October, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Resusitator, Paulton, England, #2 (2nd series), August, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Resusitator, Paulton, England, #3-4, February, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Ripple, Saint Louis, undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Road Apple Review, Albuquerque, New Mexico, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Road Apple Review, Albuquerque, New Mexico, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Road Apple Review, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 1, #3, Fall, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Road Apple Review, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 1, #4 through v. 2, #1, Winter/Spring, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Road Apple Review, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 2, #3, Fall, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Road Apple Review, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 3, #2-3, Summer/Fall, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Road Apple Review, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, v. 3, #4, Winter, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Robinson Jeffers Newsletter, Occidental College, Los Angeles, #27, November, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Rogue River Gorge, Ashland, Oregon, #1, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Rogue River Gorge, Ashland, Oregon, #2, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Ronald Reagan, London, England, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Root and Branch, Berkeley, California, Winter, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Roots Forming, Monroe, Michigan, #1, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- The Runcible Spoon, Carmichael, California, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #1, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #2, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #3, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #4, circa 1968 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #5, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #6, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #8, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #9, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #10, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #11, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, #12, undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, unnumbered issue #1, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- The Runcible Spoon, Sacramento, California, unnumbered issue #2, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Rune, Durham, North Carolina, v. 1, #1, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- S-B Gazette, Sausalito, California, #13, Spring/Summer, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- S-B Gazette, Sausalito, California, #14, Fall/Winter, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #1, October 28, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #2, November 27, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #3, January 21, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #4, February 19, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, v. 2, #1 (#5), March 5, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #6, March 26, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #9, June 16, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #13, November, 1969-December, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #14, January, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #15, February, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #16, undated (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #17, undated (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #18, mid-Summer, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Sage, Santa Fe, New Mexico, #19, Fall, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Sailing the Road Clear, Redlands, California, v. 1, August, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Sailing the Road Clear, Redlands, California, v. 2, May, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Sailing the Road Clear, Redlands, California, v. 4, December, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Saint Andrews Review, Saint Andrews Presbyterian College, Laurinburg, North Carolina, v. 1, #1, Fall/Winter, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 40)
- Saint Andrews Review, Saint Andrews Presbyterian College, Laurinburg, North Carolina, v. 2, #1, Fall/Winter, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 41)
- Saint Andrews Review, Saint Andrews Presbyterian College, Laurinburg, North Carolina, v. 3, #1, Fall/Winter, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 42)
- Salon, Guatemala, v. 2, #3, March, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 43)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #1, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 44)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #2, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 45)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #3, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 46)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #4, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 47)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #5, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 48)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #6, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 49)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #7, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 50)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #8, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 51)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #9, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 52)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #10, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 53)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, special #, undated (Box 45, Folder 54)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #1, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 55)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #2, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 56)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #3, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 57)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #4, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 58)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #5, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 59)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #6, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 60)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #7, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 61)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #8, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 62)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #10, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 63)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #1, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 64)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #2, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 65)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #3, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 66)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #4, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 67)
- The Salt Creek Reader, Lincoln, Nebraska, #6, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 68)
- Salt Lick, Baltimore, #6, October, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 69)
- Salt Lick, Baltimore, #9-10, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 70)
- Samisdat, San Jose, California, v. 9, #4 (#33, Solstice, Paul Payack), 1976 (Box 45, Folder 71)
- Samisdat, San Jose, California, v. 13, #2 (#49, Solstice II, Paul Payack), 1976 (Box 45, Folder 72)
- Samphire, Ipswich, England, #10, October, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 73)
- San Fernando Poetry Journal, Northridge, California, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 74)
- San Fernando Poetry Journal, Northridge, California, v. 1, #2, Summer, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 75)
- The San Francisco Earthquake, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, Fall, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- The San Francisco Earthquake, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- The San Francisco Earthquake, San Francisco, v. 1, #3, Spring, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- The San Francisco Earthquake, San Francisco, v. 1, #4, Summer/Fall, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- The San Francisco Earthquake, San Francisco, #5, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- San Francisco Gallery, San Francisco, #1, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- San Miguel Review, Guanajuata, Mexico, v. 2, #2, June, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Sand Script, San Bruno, California, #1, February, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Sanskaras, Clark, New Jersey, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Satis, Newcastle upon Tyne, England, #3, Summer, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Satis, Newcastle upon Tyne, England, #4, Winter, 1961-1962 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- The Savage, Chicago, #1, Spring/Summer, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- The Savage, Chicago, #2, Winter, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Scotia, Lyth, by Wick, Scotland, #23, November, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Scotia, Lyth, by Wick, Scotland, #24, December, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Scottish International, Edinburgh, Scotland, January, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Scottish International, Edinburgh, Scotland, #2, April, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Scottish International, Edinburgh, Scotland, #3, August, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Scottish International, Edinburgh, Scotland, #4, October, 1968-November, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Scottish International, Edinburgh, Scotland, #5, January, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Scraps, Fresno, California, #1, undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Scree, Missoula, Montana, #2, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Scree, Missoula, Montana, #3, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Scree, South Slocar, Canada, February, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Scree, South Slocar, Canada, July, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Screen Door Review, Onondaga, Michigan, #1, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Seaplane, New York City, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Search for Tomorrow, Iowa City, Iowa, #1, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Search for Tomorrow, Iowa City, Iowa, #2, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Search for Tomorrow, Iowa City, Iowa, #3, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Search for Tomorrow, Iowa City, Iowa, #4-5, Spring, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Sebastian Quill, San Francisco, #3, Summer, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- The Second Aeon, Cardiff, Wales, #7, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
- The Second Aeon, Cardiff, Wales, #8-9, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
- The Second Aeon, Cardiff, Wales, #11, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
- The Second Aeon, Cardiff, Wales, #12, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Second Coming, San Francisco, #1, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Second Coming, San Francisco, v. 2, #3, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Second Coming, San Francisco, v. 3, #1-2, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- The Second Wave, Boston, v. 4, #3, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #33, August 20, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #35, September 20, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #37, October, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #38, October, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #39, October, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #40, October, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #41, October, 1964-December, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Seed, Canton, Missouri, #56, January 15, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Sens Plastique, France, March, 1959-April, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 17)